

Summary

UTCN Automation and Computers student, interested in anything involving IT

. Excellent research, time management and problem solving skills.

Highly organized with the ability to manage multiple projects and consistently meet deadlines.

To have a better look at my projects, I suggest looking through my github profile : https://github.com/laurentiubig

Core Competencies

Self-Learner

Initiative

Flexibility

Team Building / Leadership

Analytical Thinking

Stress Management

Conceptual Thinking

Thoroughness

Education

Automation and Computers in English

2017 - 2021

UTCN Automatics and Computers

I had chose this field in favor of computer science and automation because I wanted to learn hardware as well as software

Mathematics and Informatics

2013 - 2017

Liceul Teoretic Lucian Blaga Cluj Napoca

Work experience

Fullstack Developer

2019-10 - 2020-04

Paddy Power Betfair

It was a new and positive experience working at Betfair, I was surrounded with a fun environment and great people who taught me some new concepts for :

Backend - Java with the following technologies: maven, sping.

Fronted - mostly VueJs, Angular and some ReactJs.

QA testing - with the following technologies: Junit, selenium, mockito, jenkins, Jest

Scrum agile methodology.

Arhitecture of deployment environment - build and deploy artifacts.

Web server load management

etc

Web Developer 2018-05 - 2019-05

Simbound

Web Developer Simbound Implement new features for the Simbound Simulation using the following technologies:

HTML, CSS ,PHP ,MySQL JavaScript, jQuery, React .

Work in team using Git for version control

Come with new ideas for making the experience as pleasant as possible

Configure the server for my needs(Ex. git deployment)

Skills JavaScript, JQuery HTML & CSS PHP & MySql Java Junit,Jest Git VueJs, Angular, Reactis C C#, C++ Linear Algebra, Calculus and Geometry **English Language Level** Spanish Language Level



- -Playing Video Games
- -Technologies
- -Mathematics
- -Fitness
- -Reading books, Comics

Created with 🔁 VisualCV